<mediawiki xmlns="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/ http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11.xsd" version="0.11" xml:lang="en">
<page>
  <title>Regions/ja</title>
  <ns>0</ns>
  <id>12355</id>
  <revision>
    <id>34595</id>
    <timestamp>2022-12-13T23:33:45Z</timestamp>
    <text space="preserve" bytes="7866">&lt;languages/&gt;
'''地方'''とは、ポケモンの世界にある地域のこと。新しい地方には、 [[Route Statistics|ルート]], [[Towns &amp; Cities|町]], [[Gyms|ジム]]、[[Obtainable Pokémon|ポケモン]]が登場します。
その地方に生息していないポケモンはダメージデバフを受けますが、新しい地方に入るたびにこのデバフは10%ずつ減少します。さらに、地域によっては独自のゲームプレイが可能です。

&lt;span id="Kanto"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
===[[Kanto|カントー地方]]===

カントーは最初の地域で、プレイヤーにゲームプレイの核となる機能を紹介します。151匹のポケモンが登場し、捕まえて育てることができます。
ポケモンの[[Pokemon Day Care|育成や孵化]]、[[Underground|地底]]での発掘、[[Farm|農場]]での[[Berries|きのみ]]の栽培、[[Quests|クエスト]]のクリア、[[Oak Items|オークアイテム]]の使用、[[Gems|ジェム]]、[[Achievements|実績]]など、段階を踏んでプレイヤーに紹介していきます。
入手したポケモンに[[Protein|プロテイン]]を与えることで、1回の育成で追加されるダメージ量が増加します。
プロテインは、カントー地方終盤の [[Shops#Kanto: Locations &amp; Items|セキエイこうげん]]で入手できます。

カントー地方ならではの特徴として、プレイヤーが自由に移動してポケモンを捕まえることができる[[Safari Zone|サファリゾーン]]があり、石を投げて捕獲確率を上げたり、エサを与えて逃げる確率を下げたりすることができます。

'''他地方ポケモンのダメージデバフ：80%'''&lt;br&gt;
'''ポケモン1匹あたりの最大プロテイン：5個'''

&lt;span id="Johto"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
===[[Johto|ジョウト地方]]===

ジョウトは、プレイヤーがさらに100種類のポケモンを捕まえることができる2番目の地域です。ジョウトで新たに導入される機能は育成キューです。
ダメージデバフが顕著になる最初の地域であり、他地方のポケモンには、発見された地域の数に応じてダメージデバフがかかります。関東を含む訪問した地域ごとに、デバフが10%減少します。例：カントーで全体ダメージが10,000だったポケモンは、ジョウトでは2,000に減少します。ジョウトに生息するポケモンは、ジョウトで100%のダメージを与える。[[Dock|ドック]]を経由してカントーに移動した場合は、その逆となります。ジョウトのポケモンはカントーで20％、カントーのポケモンはカントーで100％のダメージを与えることができます。&lt;br&gt;
育成キューでは、現在育成中の4匹のタマゴの他に、4匹のポケモンをキューに入れることができます。このポケモンは、育成した時点でチーム全体のダメージ量に加算されなくなり、育成して孵化させるか、育成キューから外すかしないといけません。&lt;br&gt;
ジョウトでは、プレイヤーは農場を盛り上げるために、もう1つオークアイテムを手に入れる機会があります。

'''他地方ポケモンのダメージデバフ：80%'''&lt;br&gt;
'''育成キュー：4'''&lt;br&gt;
'''ポケモン1匹あたりの最大プロテイン：5個'''

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
===[[Hoenn]]===
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
Hoenn is the third region and the player can catch another 135 unique Pokèmon here. The player will find the last missing Oak item here and can take the challenge of the [[Battle Frontier|Battle Frontier]]. There is also a Pokémon that evolves based on the current weather here.&lt;br&gt;
In the Battle Frontier the player can take a challenge and win great prizes, including 4 unique Pokémon. It is not necessary for the progression to Sinnoh to capture these Pokémon from the Battle Frontier. To reach the last prize at stage 386 the player should have a minimum of 1,000,000 attack damage including all [[Gems|gems]] at maximum. Manual clicks are not possible in the Battle Frontier.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
'''Damage debuff of non-native Pokémon: 70%'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Breeding Queue in the hatchery: 8'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Maximum Protein per Pokémon: 15'''
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
===[[Sinnoh]]===
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
Sinnoh is the fourth region and 107 unique Pokémon are waiting to be caught. The player will encounter some Pokémon that only evolve when they are in a certain area. One should pay attention to the hints from the local people. At this stage it is suggested to give maximum [[Protein|protein]] at least to the Pokémon that are actively being bred. After clearing the [[Distortion World]] for the first time the player will be given [[Pokérus]] to their starter.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
'''Damage debuff of non-native Pokémon: 60%'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Breeding Queue in the hatchery: 16'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Maximum Protein per Pokémon: 20'''
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
===[[Unova]]===
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
Unova is the fifth region with 156 unique Pokémon to catch. There are lots of dungeons in this region that require a substantial amount of Dungeon Tokens as well as damage. Breeding and hatching Pokémon that are native to this region for several days is quite common at this stage.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
'''Damage debuff of non-native Pokémon: 50%'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Breeding Queue in the hatchery: 32'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Maximum Protein per Pokémon: 25'''
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
===[[Kalos]]===
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
Kalos is the sixth region and has 72 unique Pokémon to catch, breed and hatch. Some currently unobtainable forms will be added in the future. Kalos' gyms and dungeons are quite tough but offer great rewards as well. At this stage it should be easily possible for the player to give every Pokémon the maximum amount of protein.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
'''Damage debuff of non-native Pokémon: 40%'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Breeding Queue in the hatchery: 64'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Maximum Protein per Pokémon: 30'''
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
===[[Alola]]===
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
Alola is the seventh region and currently has 104 new Pokémon to catch, breed and hatch. Alola gyms and dungeons are quite tough but offer great rewards as well. At this stage it should be easily possible for the player to give every Pokémon the maximum amount of protein.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
'''Damage debuff of non-native Pokémon: 30%'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Breeding Queue in the hatchery: 96'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Maximum Protein per Pokémon: 35'''
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
===[[Galar]]===
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
Galar is the eighth region and currently has 108 new Pokémon to catch, breed and hatch. Galar gyms and dungeons are quite tough but offer great rewards as well. At this stage it should be easily possible for the player to give every Pokémon the maximum amount of protein. This region also introduces a new mechanic, The [[Battle Café]].&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
'''Damage debuff of non-native Pokémon: 20%'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Breeding Queue in the hatchery: 128'''&lt;br&gt;
'''Maximum Protein per Pokémon: 40'''
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div lang="en" dir="ltr" class="mw-content-ltr"&gt;
[[Category:Regions]]
&lt;/div&gt;</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>NobbHero</username>
      <id>196</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>34593</parentid>
    <sha1>cc5e9bd6605a623bfefacd96f24e594f56aa46b2</sha1>
  </revision>
</page></mediawiki>