<mediawiki xmlns="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/ http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11.xsd" version="0.11" xml:lang="en">
<page>
  <title>Help:Editing</title>
  <ns>12</ns>
  <id>21</id>
  <revision>
    <id>33453</id>
    <timestamp>2022-12-11T22:46:17Z</timestamp>
    <text space="preserve" bytes="3365">&lt;jwplayer media-id="QEcpA5SI" /&gt;{{UCP update}}
[[File:VisualEditor.png|thumb|250px|The VisualEditor]]
[[File:Wikia editor2.png|thumb|250px|The classic editor]]
'''Editing''' on Fandom is as simple as clicking the "'''{{int:edit}}'''" button on a page. Doing so will take you to an edit page where you can make changes to the page and add new information and media, correct errors, or update the formatting.

Depending on whether you are [[Help:Logging in|logged in]] or not, you may receive a different editing experience:

;&lt;big&gt;[[Help:VisualEditor]]&lt;/big&gt;
: Most anonymous and newer users will see the '''VisualEditor'''. It's an editing experience based around showing you an accurate visual representation of your changes.

;&lt;big&gt;[[Help:Classic editor]]&lt;/big&gt;
: Other users will see the classic editor, including the older visual editing experience and basic source [[Help:wikitext|wikitext]] editing.

Wikis on the UCP framework will have a different editing experience.
[[File:New Visual Editor.png|thumb|250px|The VisualEditor on a UCP wiki]]
[[File:New Source Editor.png|thumb|250px|The source editor on a UCP wiki]]
[[File:Source Editor at Mobile.jpg|thumb|250px|The source editor on a Mobile]]
[[File:VisualEditor at Mobile.jpg|thumb|250px|The VisualEditor on a Mobile]]

== Quick tips ==
* Once you are in an editor, you can use the available tools to quickly add and remove information, change the formatting, add new images and videos, update the page's layout, and much more! Once you're done making your changes, just click the "'''{{int:visualeditor-toolbar-savedialog}}'''" button to update the page.
* Don't be afraid if you "break" anything. All edits to a page are stored in the [[Help:page history|page history]], and if something does go wrong you can simply [[Help:Reverting|revert to an older version]].
* If you want to edit a page without clicking the "'''{{int:edit}}'''" button, you can press {{Hotkey|E}} on your keyboard, and the page will automatically load the preferred editor.
* Editing is not yet possible through the [[Help:Fandom app|Fandom app]].

== Choosing an editor ==
Logged in users can choose their default editor from a dropdown list in their [[Help:Preferences|user preferences]] (found [[Special:Preferences#mw-prefsection-editing|here]]).

{| class="article-table"
|-
! Setting
! Meaning
|-
! VisualEditor
| Shows the VisualEditor on all communities.
|-
! Classic rich-text editor&lt;br /&gt;(where available)
| Shows the classic rich-text editor where available.&lt;br /&gt;If not, the source editor is shown.
|-
! Source editor
| Shows the basic source editor on all communities.
|}
Anonymous users will almost always see the '''VisualEditor''' by default. In a few specific cases, the '''VisualEditor''' may not be available on a particular community.

Additionally, the alternative editors can still be found under the ''{{int:edit}}'' button dropdown - for example, you can still access the classic editor from the dropdown even if the '''VisualEditor''' is the default.

&lt;gallery bordercolor="transparent" hideaddbutton=true&gt;
Editbuttonwhenclassicisdefault.png|Accessing the VisualEditor, when the classic source editor or the classic rich-text editor is default.
VE-ClassicEditor.png|Accessing the classic editor, when the VisualEditor is default.
&lt;/gallery&gt;

== Further help and feedback ==
{{Help and feedback section}}</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>Razorflame</username>
      <id>9</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>/* Further help and feedback */ We don't need interwiki links here.</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>320</parentid>
    <sha1>ac6d0d9821a9663caa1a686b6b4029085901bd09</sha1>
  </revision>
</page></mediawiki>