<mediawiki xmlns="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/ http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11.xsd" version="0.11" xml:lang="en">
<page>
  <title>Help:FAQ</title>
  <ns>12</ns>
  <id>80</id>
  <revision>
    <id>33126</id>
    <timestamp>2022-12-09T17:46:11Z</timestamp>
    <text space="preserve" bytes="9438">=General:=

==Where can I play the latest version?==
https://www.pokeclicker.com/

or download the Windows client:

https://github.com/RedSparr0w/Pokeclicker-desktop/releases/latest

==Is the Dynamic Background available without the game?==
https://background.pokeclicker.com/

==What is the official Discord Server invite link?==
https://discord.gg/a6DFe4p

==My game isn't running at full speed when the window isn't active.==
This is a setting on browsers that slows down inactive windows,
You can change the browser flags, but this is '''not''' recommended,
Otherwise you can download the Windows client from here:
https://github.com/RedSparr0w/Pokeclicker-desktop/releases/latest

==How do I obtain [[Dungeon Tokens]]?==
Read the in game [[Quests#Tutorial|Tutorial]]. Set the "Caught" selector in the top left to a Pokéball type to capture Pokémon you have already caught.

=Saves:=

==Can I import my save from the previous version?==
You can only import the shinies you obtained in the previous (IshaDjicks) version.
They will only appear in your Pokemon list once re-captured
(this will not count as capturing a new shiny Pokemon)

==Will my progress be carried over on release?==
Your save file will likely be compatible with the final release.

=Rare/Shiny Pokémon:=

==What are the [[Roaming Pokémon#Odds|odds of finding a Roaming Pokémon]]?==
The chance to encounter a roaming Pokémon is 1/8192 for the first route of a region, and increases linearly up to 1/4096 for the last route of a region. "First" and "Last" refer to the [[Route Statistics|Route Order]], not the route number.

If it is a boosted route the chance is 3x of the route chance.

==What are the [[Shiny Chance#Odds|odds of finding a Shiny Pokémon]]?==
*On a Route - 1/8192
*In a [[Dungeons|Dungeon]] - 1/4096
*In the [[Safari Zone]] - 1/2048
*Using an [[Evolution Items|Evolution Item]] - 1/2048
*From a [[Shops|Shop]] - 1/1024
*From [[Pokémon Day Care|hatching]] an [[Egg]] - 1/1024
*[[Wandering Pokémon]] on the Farm - 1/1024

==Do Shiny Pokémon give any bonus to gameplay?==
Yes, they give an extra 100% bonus to Click Attack compared to the non shiny variant.

==If I breed a Shiny Pokémon will it stay shiny?==
Yes, once a Pokémon is shiny, it will always remain shiny.

==If I evolve a Shiny Pokémon will the evolution always be shiny?==
Only if you have Real Evolution [[Challenge Mode]] on, as the Pokémon transforms into the next stage. (take into account that next time you get the original Pokémon it won't be shiny) 

There is also a 1/2048 chance the evolution will be shiny. If it is not, you will need to obtain the evolutions shiny via a different method.

=Items:=

==What are the [[Small Restore|Small]]/[[Medium Restore|Medium]]/[[Large Restore|Large]] used for?==
They can be used in the [[Underground]] to restore some stamina.

==What are [[Berries]] used for?==
Berries are currently used on the [[Farm]] to grow more berries and earn [[Farm Points]]. They also have special Auras, that can provide Gameplay bonuses, can attract [[Wandering Pokémon]], and can be traded for various items.
Also can be used as bait in safari zone.

==What are [[Protein|Proteins]] used for?==
They increase the "base attack" of your Pokémon, which will gain you more damage each time you breed them.

==How many [[Oak Items|Oak Item]] slots are available?==
There is a maximum of 3 active slots.

=Gameplay:=

==How many [[Regions]] are playable?==
Currently, [[Kanto]] through [[Galar]] are able to be played.

==How do I get to the next [[Regions|Region]]?==
With the Recommended Challenges active, you must obtain all Pokémon available in the current region and then take the Blimp located at the region's starting town. (Note: See [[Challenge Mode]] for more information on Recommended Challenges)

'''Note:'''Once you go to the next region, you will not be able to go back to prior regions until you reach the [[Dock]] of the region you have entered.

==How do I increase my [[Pokémon Statistics#Click Attack|Click Attack]]?==
Each new Pokémon increases your click attack. New Shiny Pokémon also increase your click attack by 100% of the rate that a normal new Pokémon would.

==How do I unlock the [[Gyms#Gym Auto-Rebattle|Auto Battle option for Gyms]]?==
You must defeat a Gym Leader manually 100 times to unlock this feature for that Gym.

==How do I make the [[Dungeons#Dungeon_Size_Reduction|Dungeons smaller]]?==
As you clear the dungeon more times, it will become smaller.
(to a minimum of 5x5)

==How do I unlock [[Dungeons#Flash Ability|Flash in dungeons]]?==
You must clear a dungeon 200 times to unlock this feature for that Dungeon.

==Can I progress more than 1 [[Quests|Quest]] at a time?==
Yes, you can unlock up to 4 quest slots.
*Quest Level 5: 2 slots.
*Quest Level 10: 3 slots.
*Quest Level 15: 4 slots.

==Where is X location in [[Kanto]]?==
*[[Underground]]: Route 11.
*[[Pokémon Day Care|Daycare]]: Route 5, or click List on the Hatchery.
*[[Farm]]: Route 14.

==How do I unlock X location in [[Kanto]]?==
*Underground: Buy the [[Explorer Kit]] from [[Shops#Kanto: Locations &amp; Items|Cinnabar Island]].
*Daycare: Will be unlocked after reaching [[Kanto#Routes|Route 5]].
*Farm: Will be unlocked after reaching [[Kanto#Routes|Route 14]] and obtaining [[Berries]].

==Why should I be [[Pokémon Day Care|Breeding Pokémon]]?==
[[Baby Pokémon|Some Pokémon]] can only be obtained by breeding. When a Pokémon is hatched, its attack will increase by 25% of the base amount. Breeding also has higher odds of obtaining Shiny Pokémon (1/1024).

==How do I obtain x Pokémon?==
Make sure that you have completed every '''[[Regions|Route]]'''.
Make sure that you have completed every '''[[Dungeons|Dungeon]]'''.
Some Pokémon can only be obtained from '''[[Eggs]]'''.
Some Pokémon can only be obtained by using an [[Evolution Items|'''Evolution Stone''']].
Some Pokémon can only be obtained from the '''[[Safari Zone]]'''.
'''Fossil Pokémon''' can only be obtained by breeding [[Fossils]] that are obtained from the '''[[Underground]]'''
'''(Roamers)''' Some Pokémon will only '''randomly''' appear on '''routes''' as [[Roaming Pokemon]].
'''(Baby Pokémon)''' [[Baby Pokemon]] can only be obtained by breeding their immediate evolution (the next stage).
Some Pokémon can only evolve at certain times of day.
Some Pokémon can only evolve in specific locations.
Some Pokémon can only appear/evolve in specific [[Weather]].

==When is night and dusk?==
Right now there are 2 different set of night and dusk based upon main games: 

For almost everything '''day''' is from 6:00 am to 5:59 pm, '''night''' is from 6 pm to 5:59 am and '''dusk''' is from 5:00 pm to 5:59 pm

For [[Battle Café|Alcremie spins]] '''day''' is from 5:00 am to 6:59 pm, '''night''' is from 7:00 pm to 4:59 am and '''dusk''' is from 7:00 pm to 7:59 pm

=EVs and Pokérus (BETA)=
'''NOTE:''' This is a '''beta''' feature, so things will likely change in the future

==What is Pokérus, and what are EVs?==
Pokérus is a beneficial virus your Pokémon can catch. EVs increase the attack of your Pokémon.

==When do I unlock EVs?==
EVs are unlocked after defeating the Distortion World Dungeon (Sinnoh)

==How do I spread Pokérus?==
Pokérus is spread by Pokémon that are infected, to other Pokémon in the hatchery (not in the queue) that share a type with the infected Pokémon.

Neither Pokémon can be ready to hatch, nor can a Hatchery Helper be used on either Pokémon, in order to spread the virus.

==How do I gain EVs?==
EVs can be gained in a variety of ways, but are primarily gained by capturing (not breeding) Pokémon.

{|class="wikitable sortable"
! Situation !! EV gained
|-
|Base Yield || 0.1EV
|-
|Evolution Item Yield || 1EV
|-
|Wanderer Yield || 0.5EV
|-
|Shopmon Yield || 1EV
|-
|Safari Yield || 1EV
|-
|Shiny Modifier || 5×
|-
|Dungeon Modifier || 3×
|-
|Dungeon Boss Modifier || 10
|-
|Roamer Modifier || 50×
|-
|Repeatball Modifier || 5×
|} 


==What is the EV Attack Bonus?==
The EV bonus is multiplicative, and scales linearly until 1.5x (50EVs).

The bonus thereafter has diminishing returns relative to the number of EVs gained.

{|class="wikitable sortable"
!  EVs !! Damage Multiplier
|-
| 50 || 1.5x Damage
|-
| 802 || 2x Damage
|-
| 40,121 || 3x Damage
|-
| 643,300 || 4x Damage
|-
| 5,540,000 || 5x Damage
|} 

==What do the Pokérus status filters mean?==
'''None:''' Pokémon that have not been infected with Pokérus.

'''Contagious:''' Pokémon with less than 50 EVs.

'''Resistant:''' Pokémon with more than 50 EVs. These Pokémon will still be able to spread Pokérus.

=Development:=


==When will the development version be fully released?==
There are currently no plans for a "final release".
Maybe once all regions are added that will be version 1.0.0

==When will more regions be added?==
This is a priority, but there in no set timeline. It will be ready when it is ready.

==Who are the awesome people developing this game?==
The original game was developed by IshaDjicks, who has since decided to stop working on this project. Since then lots of people have helped by [[Code Contributors|Contributing Code]] via GitHub.

==How can I help with development?==
The GitHub repo is located here:
https://github.com/pokeclicker/pokeclicker.

Any new issues, suggestions or code contributions are always welcomed.
You may even earn certain [[Discord Roles]] based on your contributions.</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>CooldudeOmega0</username>
      <id>25</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>33117</parentid>
    <sha1>6cb2a0e995ec817fee77436e2242d75dc5316244</sha1>
  </revision>
</page></mediawiki>