<page>
  <title>Flutes</title>
  <ns>0</ns>
  <id>4087</id>
  <revision>
    <id>14918</id>
    <timestamp>2022-04-30T21:39:37Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="3283" space="preserve">'''Flutes''' are a series of special items each with their own beneficial effect.
Flutes are gained by purchasing them from the Hoenn and Unova Gem Master shops.

==Usage==
Activating a flute happens when the Player clicks on the flute to activate it.  Flutes can be enabled / disabled whenever the player wants.  Each Flute buffs different properties in game, and requires 3 types of Gems to power their effects.  

Activating multiple Flutes simultaneously increases the cost in gems of keeping all Flutes active.  Each active Flute costs one Gem per second, per active Flute, from the Flutes three gem categories.  However, gem type costs don't overlap, thus, activating the Grass Flute (Grass, Bug, Fairy Gems) and the White Flute (Normal, Bug, Rock Gems) requires 2 gems per second from the five gem types: Normal, Grass, Bug, Rock, and Fairy.  Keeping all 12 Flutes active thus costs 12 gems per second from every type of Gem.

Each active flute also provides a static +0.5% attack boost to the required gem types. However, like gem type costs, the attack boost does not overlap. Thus, activating the Grass Flute (Grass, Bug, Fairy Gems) and the White Flute (Normal, Bug, Rock Gems) gives a +0.5% attack boost to the following types: Normal, Grass, Bug, Rock, and Fairy. Keeping all 12 Flutes active thus gives a +0.5% attack boost to all types.


===Active Cost per Flute===
{|class="wikitable sortable"
! Flutes active !! Gem cost / s &lt;br&gt;(per Gem Type)
|-
| 1 || 1
|-
| 2 || 2
|-
| 3 || 3
|-
| 4 || 4
|-
| 5 || 5
|-
| 6 || 6
|-
| 7 || 7
|-
| 8 || 8
|-
| 9 || 9
|-
| 10 || 10
|-
| 11 || 11
|-
| 12 || 12
|}

==List of Flutes==
{|class="wikitable sortable"
! Name
! Consumed Gems
! Effect
|-
| {{Bag2|Red Flute}}
| Consumes Fighting, Fire, and Poison Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to Click Attack
|-
| {{Bag2|White Flute}}
| Consumes Normal, Bug, and Rock Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to EXP Yield
|-
| {{Bag2|Black Flute}}
| Consumes Normal, Flying, and Poison Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to Item Drop Rate
|-
| {{Bag2|Yellow Flute}}
| Consumes Dark, Electric, and Steel Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to Pokedollar Yield
|-
| {{Bag2|Blue Flute}}
| Consumes Dark, Ghost, and Ice Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to Dungeon Token Yield
|-
| {{Bag2|Poke Flute}}
| Consumes Fighting, Ice, and Fairy Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to Pokemon Attack
|-
| {{Bag2|Azure Flute}}
| Consumes Dragon, Ghost, and Steel Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to Shiny Chance
|-
| {{Bag2|Eon Flute}}
| Consumes Flying, Dragon, and Psychic Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to Roaming Chance
|-
| {{Bag2|Sun Flute}}
| Consumes Fire, Ground, and Water Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to Egg Steps
|-
| {{Bag2|Moon Flute}}
| Consumes Rock, Ground, and Electric Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to Mining Energy Regeneration Yield and Time
|-
| {{Bag2|Time Flute}}
| Consumes Grass, Psychic, and Water Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to Dungeon Timer
|-
| {{Bag2|Grass Flute}}
| Consumes Grass, Bug, and Fairy Gems
| (2% x (1 + Achievement Bonus)) Bonus to Berry Replant and Growth Multipliers
|-
|}


{{Battle items}}&lt;br&gt;
[[Category:Flutes]] [[Category:Items]]</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>LatiosRider</username>
      <id>35</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>/* Added paragraph explaining the type boosting effect */</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>14917</parentid>
    <sha1>91dcdbde0517f1f020e181219676177eaaed5eb4</sha1>
  </revision>
</page>