<page>
  <title>To-Do list</title>
  <ns>0</ns>
  <id>802</id>
  <revision>
    <id>8915</id>
    <timestamp>2021-10-03T04:41:25Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="15859" space="preserve">Welcome to our To-Do list where we try and keep a track of everything which needs fixing/updating/adding/removing and anything else in any of the pages of the wiki. If you see something that needs to be done on any of the pages, feel free to edit this page and it in the below list or simply drop a message in our [https://discord.gg/a6DFe4p Discord] and someone else will do it.
&lt;br&gt;

We aim to one day have this page empty but it is not so easy unless everyone contributes a little.
&lt;br&gt;

Please do not delete the task if done, just write (DONE) before it so that one of the moderators can verify it.

== Uncategorized Tasks ==

== Categorized Tasks ==

These task are also put together with like tasks so multiple tasks on one page can be done by 1 person all at once rather than multiple people over a long period of time because of misplaced information.

''Page Creation'' is the creation of an entire page, and then adding all the information, adding lots of images to pages, or just large undertakings of fairly blank pages.
''Finishing Touches'' is for pages that are missing a small bit of info, or need to have a few images uploaded to them.
''Updating'' is for pages that were afflicted by the most recent update of the game, and thus have to be checked for informational inaccuracies.
''Formatting'' is for pages that would need to have their infoboxes changes, the way the information is display, or the general aesthetic changed.

=== Page Creation ===

== Dream tasks ==
These tasks are so long and such low priority that it is more of a dream to complete them.

# add battle item type template for other pages in these headings, "Key items", "shop of each region" and any more that can be put under same big heading.
# add Shiny Variants to the normal Pokémon and a way to swap between the images.  This is something that's up to debate, as there's little use for it other than being something for us to do.

== Completed tasks awaiting moderators ==

# '''DONE''' in [[Quests]] Page, add the value of the Mine Items Quest, it's location where the value can be found is noted on the page.
# '''DONE''' Add the Quest EXP gain system, and the required Quests to reach each level.
# '''DONE''' Upload High Resolution images for DNA Splicers and Shard Case, update images on each respective Key Item page.
# '''DONE''' Fix Wobbufett's uploaded image
# '''DONE''' create a [[Key Items]] page listing all key items of the game.
# '''DONE''' in [[Lum]], elaborate the "Strategy and important notes" section of the page.
# '''DONE''' Update [[Baby Pokémon]] for Unova Pokémon
# '''DONE''' Update [[Shards]] for Unova gyms
# '''DONE''' Update [[Events]] for Santa Snorlax Event
# '''DONE''' Add Unova roamers to [[Roaming Pokémon]]
# '''DONE''' Add Unova egg Pokémon to [[Egg]]
# '''DONE''' Add Unova gyms to [[Gyms]]
# '''DONE''' Add Unova NPCs to [[NPCs]]
# '''DONE''' Add Unova shops to [[Shops]]
# '''DONE''' Ensure all berry page infoboxes have a berrydex index in them
# '''DONE''' Check and fix Egg Cycles, Attack Cycle, and Egg Steps for Gen 6, 7, and 8 Pokémon in [[List of Pokemons with attack]] (Note: This is due to the latest breeding patch)
# '''DONE''' Add alternate forms and event exclusive Pokémon to [[List of Pokemons with attack]]
# '''DONE''' Add Catch Rate column to all tables in [[List of Pokemons with attack]]
# '''DONE''' [[Unova]] Page created
# '''DONE''' Add Unova Towns and cities to [[Towns &amp; Cities]]
# '''DONE''' Update all region route lists for optimal shard farming as of version 7.0.0
# '''DONE''' Deleted the second [[Item Magnet]] to make it just say [[Item Magnet]] instead of Item Magnet Item Magnet in [[Battle Frontier]] page in the upgrades section
# '''DONE''' Create all Unova dungeon pages
# '''DONE''' in [[Babiri]] page, add the aura effect
# '''DONE''' in [[Petaya]] page, add the aura effect that while this berry is ripe, it prevents all nearby berry from dying.
# '''DONE''' in [[Events]] page, ad more details about what events are and what we look for in planning new events if someone wanna propose any idea
# '''DONE''' Create [[Template:Infobox egg]] and add to all egg pages
# '''DONE''' Create [[Template:Infobox evolution item]] and add to all evolution item pages
# '''DONE''' Add Unova purchase locations to all item pages
# '''DONE''' Add Unova routes to [[Route Statistics]]
# '''DONE''' Add to [[Poke_Dollar|Pokédollar]] page, preferably detailed information like [[Dungeon Tokens]].
# '''DONE''' Add somewhere that egg steps in the Battle Frontier are the square root of the stage number
# '''DONE''' Add Unova [[Protein]] efficiency table
# '''DONE''' Add Unova to [[Dungeon Tokens]]
# '''DONE''' add a growth table for each berry timings with maxed sprayduck or boost mulch equipped, they both give same boost so only one table will show time for both conditions (see example page [[Roseli]])
# '''DONE''' add a growth table for each berry timing with both maxed sprayduck and boost mulch active (see example page [[Roseli]])
# '''DONE''' Write how many total boost mulch each berry need to have the boost active with boost mulch alone (see example page [[Roseli]])
# '''DONE''' Write how many total boost mulch each berry need to have the boost active with both boost mulch &amp; maxed sprayduck (see example page [[Roseli]])
# '''DONE''' add timing table for berries that need multiple berries to be ripe at the same time (see example page [[Roseli]])
# '''DONE''' make [[Berry Master]] page better, its too blank and raw right now.
# '''DONE''' in [[Underground]] page, add a infobox on right showing the underground, update the efficiency section image with new underground image.
# '''DONE''' Add the Cover and Plume Fossil underground tile images (in block format like the other fossils) to [[Fossils]]
# '''DONE''' in [[Type and shard effectiveness]] page, the "practicality" section of the page need a clearer text explanation.
# '''DONE''' Add images of Pokémon before their names in these pages
# '''DONE''' In underground page, add what Pokémon's drop Moon stones.
# '''DONE''' update Shops page to show new oak items
# '''DONE''' in [[Sprayduck]] page, the cost of lvling is not berries and should be changed to "harvested Plots".
# '''DONE''' Add new Burmy forms and Unown forms to [[List of Pokemons with attack]].
# '''DONE''' For Berries 9-20 add the purple color (example [[Roseli]]) to the planting diagram.
# '''DONE''' Update [[Underground]] Images
# '''DONE''' Update [[Shards]] Images
# '''DONE''' Update [[Help:FAQ|FAQ]].
# '''DONE''' Check all [[Dungeons]] pages to make sure HP values are correct. Hoenn and Sinnoh need fixes
# '''DONE''' (Low priority) in [[Starf]] berry page, in the planting formation section, make it so that the 2 empty plots are somewhere in middle and also mention that getting passho before starf might be a good idea. Can go a step further and mention that harvesting a starf surrounded by 8 passho+rich mulch gives 8 starf berry yield.
# '''DONE''' &lt;s&gt;Add encounter weights to every [[Dungeons]]&lt;/s&gt; All Encounter weights are approximately the same for each dungeon, this rate was added to [[Dungeons]] under "How to Clear"
# '''DONE''' in [[Underground]] page, in the heading Upgrades, add a single line description of what each upgrade does when purchased.
# '''DONE''' in [[Underground]] page, in the heading Items, add a small description of what is "held item drop"
# '''DONE''' Add trainers (and images of trainers which are uploaded already) to every [[Dungeons]].
# '''DONE''' in [[Towns &amp; Cities]] page, write which city is on what route preferably in a table 
# '''DONE''' [[Shard Case]] page created, needs to be formatted in the same way and use the same templates as the other [[Key Items]]. See [[Wailmer Pail]] for referenceformat.
# '''DONE''' Remove Efficiency in [[Underground]] page as no efficiency is workable after update v0.7.4. [New Efficiency Created]
# '''DONE''' [[Underground]] page, in the heading Items, the Mine layout column is no longer completely true as items can appear rotated, so either remove the column or add layout for all possible rotation of the items. [Designated that they could be rotated]
# '''DONE''' Add [[Solaceon Ruins]] to [[Dungeons]].
# '''DONE''' add the Cost to [[Oak Items]] that are Purchasable.
# '''DONE''' Add an Infobox to [[Shards]] displaying an image of the in game Shard Case
# '''DONE''' Add a list of all the berries in each berries which need that berry for mutations. Such as list all berries that need Razz berry to mutate in the Razz berry page.
# '''DONE''' Add all the egg images next to their respective Pokémon in the [[List of Pokemons with attack]] page
# '''DONE''' check every page that use PokeCoin.png and make the image appear after the amount.
# '''DONE''' Add Kalos to the Towns &amp; Cities page
# '''DONE''' Sachet - page created
# '''DONE''' Whipped Dream - page created
# '''DONE''' Added Kalos locations to Evolution items
# '''DONE''' NPC page - Kalos added
# '''DONE''' Roaming Pokémon page - Kalos added
# '''DONE''' Dock page - Kalos added
# '''DONE''' Towns &amp; Cities page - Roamer NPCs &amp; missing dungeons added
# '''DONE''' Gyms page - Kalos added
# '''DONE''' Starf requierements updated
# '''DONE''' Make a proper [[Regions]] page, listing and giving brief info of all available regions.
# '''DONE''' Create [[Pokéball Bag]], [[Coin Case]], [[Town Map]], and [[Teachy TV]] Key Item Pages. (Format the same as [[Wailmer Pail]]
# '''DONE''' [[Rare hold items]] should have drop chances added to the side of each item, along with the item magnet boosted chance (This is up to debate on the Wiki-General because of the effect it may have on the page look)
# '''DONE''' Make the [[Johto]] Page like all the other regions, or vice-versa.
# '''DONE''' Add how long for weather to change and for the roamer person to change the route they talk about
# '''DONE''' Add acquisition table to all [[Evolution Items]] (Accomplished on new Evolution Items consolidated page)
# '''DONE''' Added health of Pokémon at each reward level in [[Battle Frontier]], did not add further levels or base attack approximations
# '''DONE''' Add Flabebé Blue and Yellow to [[Berries]]
# '''DONE''' Re-evaluate the Shards Page as of Kalos release
# '''DONE''' Create [[Achievements]] page. Include all unique achievement types.
# '''DONE''' Add trainers to all [[Hoenn]] and [[Unova]] Dungeons. Also add trainers to [[Dungeons]]
# '''DONE''' Wandering Pokémon added to main berry page
# '''DONE''' Write the specifics of how breeding efficiency is calculated (It's on [[Protein]])
# '''DONE''' Created [[Pokemon Day Care]] page, needs image of the Hatchery modal and revisions/additions to the text.
# '''DONE''' Add an Infobox to [[Pokemon Day Care]] displaying an image of the in game Hatchery
# '''DONE''' in each region's page, add a walkthrough-like flowchart (preferably in text format) showing what unlocks what as a player progress on map.
# '''DONE''' [https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1l74KcfoY3Qs97RLJLwnpJYWcy2RzQ79e?usp=sharing|Berry Flow Charts] created for all berries except Apicot and Lansat (unimplemented)
# '''DONE''' Add the amount of Evolution stones needed in each region on its respective regional page, and then on the Evolution Items Page (Added to [[Quest Points]], can be added to regional pages but it's probably fine like this)
# '''DONE''' Add note about level caps for Gyms to [[Kanto]] and to [[Gyms]] (Just put in on [[Gyms]] for now, could add elsewhere)
# '''DONE''' Make a subsection of the most efficient breeding/shiny farm to account for laziness/timeliness sake as well as the top 5 or 10 most efficient methods (if you think this to be a viable thing) - Done on [[Shiny Chance]] and [[Pokemon Day Care]]
# '''DONE''' Fix the [[Petaya]] setup because [[Kasib]] only shortens adjacent berry death timers - could be refined further, timings with Haban + Yache are hard
# '''DONE''' Format all [[Regions]] pages like [[Kanto]]. Include the exclusive Pokémon categories, and add any additional subsections that are necessary
# '''DONE''' Write out the rough amount of DPS necessary to defeat each of the gym leaders, elite 4, and champions. ''Added in [[Gyms]]''
# '''DONE''' Fix item images on [[Underground]] and [[Diamonds]] to reflect dream world sprites in game menu
# '''DONE''' Add Vivillon Quest Line to [[Quests]]
# '''DONE''' Update [[Gyms]] and [[Poke Dollar]] to reflect Nerfed/Buffed Gym Money
# '''DONE''' Add the mutation rate of each [[Berry]] to the Berry Infobox at the top of each individual Berry page
# '''DONE''' Update formulas on [[Protein]] and any other pages with mathematical equations using the Math function used on [[Battle Frontier]]
# '''DONE''' Upload all Vivillon Egg Patterns for [[List of Pokémon with attack]]
# '''DONE''' Create [[Pokémon with Alternate Forms]] Page
# '''DONE''' Update [[Berries]] to 0.8.4
# '''DONE''' Update [[Route Statistics]] to 0.8.4
# '''DONE''' Update [[Poke Dollar]] to 0.8.4
# '''DONE''' Update [[Dungeon Tokens]] to 0.8.4
# '''DONE''' Update Vivillon Image to 0.8.4
# '''DONE''' Update [[Achievements]] to 0.8.4
# '''DONE''' Make Flow Charts for [[Apicot]] and [[Lansat]]
# '''DONE''' Add explanation of Dual-Type Effectiveness to [[Type and shard effectiveness]]
# '''DONE''' Update [[Quests]] to 0.8.4
# '''DONE''' Update Capture Pokémon Types Quest in [[Quests]]
{| role="presentation" class="wikitable mw-collapsible mw-collapsed"
|List of pages that need Pokémon images (Complete up to at least version 0.7.1)
|-
|'''[[Baby Pokémon]]''', '''[[Burned Tower]]''', '''[[Cave of Origin]]''', '''[[Cerulean Cave]]''', '''[[Dark Cave]]''', '''[[Dawn Stone]]''', '''[[Deepsea Scale]]''', '''[[Deepsea Tooth]]''', '''[[Digletts Cave]]''', '''[[Distortion World]]''', '''[[Dragon Egg]]''', '''[[Dragon Scale]]''', '''[[Dubious Disc]]''', '''[[Egg]]''', '''[[Electric Egg]]''', '''[[Eterna Forest]]''', '''[[Fiery Path]]''', '''[[Fighting Egg]]''', '''[[Fire Egg]]''', '''[[Fire Stone]]''', '''[[Flower Paradise]]''', '''[[Fossils]]''', '''[[Fullmoon Island]]''', '''[[Granite Cave]]''', '''[[Grass Egg]]''', '''[[Hall of Origin]]''', '''[[Hoenn]]''', '''[[Ice Path]]''', '''[[Ilex Forest]]''', '''[[Iron Island]]''', '''[[Jagged Pass]]''', '''[[Johto]]''', '''[[Kanto]]''', '''[[Kings Rock]]''', '''[[Lake Acuity]]''', '''[[Lake Valor]]''', '''[[Lake Verity]]''', '''[[Leaf Stone]]''', '''[[List of Pokemons with attack]]''', '''[[Magmarizer]]''', '''[[Metal Coat]]''', '''[[Moon Stone]]''', '''[[Mt. Chimney]]''', '''[[Mt. Coronet North]]''', '''[[Mt. Coronet South]]''', '''[[Mt. Moon]]''', '''[[Mt. Pyre]]''', '''[[Mt Mortar]]''', '''[[Mt Silver]]''', '''[[New Mauville]]''', '''[[Newmoon Island]]''', '''[[Old Chateau]]''', '''[[Oreburgh Gate]]''', '''[[Petalburg Woods]]''', '''[[Pokemon Mansion]]''', '''[[Pokemon Tower]]''', '''[[Power Plant]]''', '''[[Prism Scale]]''', '''[[Protector]]''', '''[[Protein]]''', '''[[Ravaged Path]]''', '''[[Razor Claw]]''', '''[[Razor Fang]]''', '''[[Reaper Cloth]]''', '''[[Roaming Pokémon]]''', '''[[Rock Tunnel]]''', '''[[Ruins of Alph]]''', '''[[Rusturf Tunnel]]''', '''[[Safari Zone]]''', '''[[Seafloor Cavern]]''', '''[[Seafoam Islands]]''', '''[[Sealed Chamber]]''', '''[[Shiny Stone]]''', '''[[Shoal Cave]]''', '''[[Shops]]''', '''[[Sinnoh]]''', '''[[Sky Pillar]]''', '''[[Slowpoke Well]]''', '''[[Snowpoint Temple]]''', '''[[Soothe Bell]]''', '''[[Spear Pillar]]''', '''[[Sprout Tower]]''', '''[[Stark Mountain]]''', '''[[Sun Stone]]''', '''[[Thunder Stone]]''', '''[[Tin Tower]]''', '''[[Trade Stone]]''', '''[[Union Cave]]''', '''[[Upgrade]]''', '''[[Unova]]''', '''[[Victory Road]]''', '''[[Victory Road Hoenn]]''', '''[[Victory Road Sinnoh]]''', '''[[Viridian Forest]]''', '''[[Water Egg]]''', '''[[Water Stone]]''', '''[[Wayward Cave]]''', '''[[Whirl Islands]]''', '''[[Weather]]'''
|}</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>GarrikFel</username>
      <id>23</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>Update Capture Pokémon Types Quest in [[Quests]]</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>8914</parentid>
    <sha1>80e6e1005e7b9eacbd3ead39558cb158682a48b9</sha1>
  </revision>
</page>