<page>
  <title>Farm</title>
  <ns>0</ns>
  <id>191</id>
  <revision>
    <id>3216</id>
    <timestamp>2020-11-17T00:09:37Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="3575" space="preserve">[[File:Pokeclicker_Farm_Interface.png|400px|thumb|The Farm interface, with Cheri Berries selected.]]

The '''Farm''' is a location in Kanto where [[Berries]] can be planted. Harvesting them yields [[Pokemon Dollars|money]], [[Farming Points]], and more of the same type of Berry. Occasionally, mutations can occur when berries are planted in certain configurations. The Farm is unlocked upon unlocking Route 14 of [[Kanto]] and obtaining the [[Wailmer pail]].

One of the quests that can appear involves harvesting a random amount of a certain type of Berry.

=Usage=

''For a breakdown of harvest yields, flavors, and mutation configurations for the various types of Berries, consult the [[Berries]] page.

Before completing Kanto, the Farm can be accessed by clicking on its location on the map between Routes 14 and 15, but upon reaching Johto, it becomes available in the Shortcuts dropdown list.

The eight base Berries are dropped by defeated Pokemon at random. They can be planted by selecting the desired type in the left-hand column and clicking on plots in the field on the right. Alternatively, the "Plant All" button can be clicked to plant the selected Berry in every empty plot.

Depending on the type of Berry planted, different lengths of time have to pass before they can be harvested. Individual plots can be clicked to be harvested, or the "Harvest All" button may be pressed to harvest every plot ready for harvesting.

When Berry plants become ripe, they will die after a set period of time if not harvested. When this happens, only a fraction of the harvest is obtained, and there is a chance they will replant themselves, spawning a plant of the same berry in that plot. This chance can be augmented by using the Sprinklotad Oak Item.

Special Berries can be obtained by planting other Berries in special configurations. The Kanto Berry Master in Cerulean City gives hints as to these configurations. The chance for mutations to occur can be augmented by the Squirtbottle Oak Item.

Mulch and Shovels can be bought in Goldenrod City (Johto), Mauville City (Hoenn), Hearthome City (Sinnoh). Mulch can be applied to growing Berry plants to speed up growth, increase harvest yield, increase mutation chance, or all of the above with reduced effect. Shovels can be used to free up occupied plots.

=Upgrades=

Extra plots can be unlocked by spending Farming Points and Berries to allow more Berries to grow simultaneously, up to a maximum of 25. The table below displays the cost to unlock each plot corresponding to the 5x5 grid of plots in the Farm.

{| class="wikitable"
|-
| 220 Kelpsy&lt;br \&gt;4840 {{Farmpoints}} || rowspan = 5 | || 170 Mago&lt;br \&gt;2890 {{Farmpoints}} || rowspan = 5 | || 90 Persim&lt;br \&gt;810 {{Farmpoints}} || rowspan = 5 | || 130 Wepear&lt;br \&gt;1690 {{Farmpoints}} || rowspan = 5 | || 230 Qualot&lt;br \&gt;5290 {{Farmpoints}}
|-
| 160 Wiki&lt;br \&gt;2560 {{Farmpoints}} || 50 Aspear&lt;br \&gt;250 {{Farmpoints}} || 10 Cheri&lt;br \&gt;10 {{Farmpoints}} || 60 Leppa&lt;br \&gt;360 {{Farmpoints}} || 180 Aguav&lt;br \&gt;3240 {{Farmpoints}}
|-
| 120 Nanab&lt;br \&gt;1440 {{Farmpoints}} || 40 Rawst&lt;br \&gt;160 {{Farmpoints}} || Free || 20 Chesto&lt;br \&gt;40 {{Farmpoints}} || 100 Razz&lt;br \&gt;1000 {{Farmpoints}}
|-
| 210 Pomeg&lt;br \&gt;4410 {{Farmpoints}} || 80 Sitrus&lt;br \&gt;640 {{Farmpoints}} || 30 Pecha&lt;br \&gt;90 {{Farmpoints}} || 70 Oran&lt;br \&gt;490 {{Farmpoints}} || 140 Pinap&lt;br \&gt;1960 {{Farmpoints}}
|-
| 250 Grepa&lt;br \&gt;6250 {{Farmpoints}} || 150 Figy&lt;br \&gt;2250 {{Farmpoints}} || 110 Bluk&lt;br \&gt;1210 {{Farmpoints}} || 190 Iapapa&lt;br \&gt;3610 {{Farmpoints}} || 240 Hondew&lt;br \&gt;5760 {{Farmpoints}}
|}</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>J-3047</username>
      <id>42</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>3215</parentid>
    <sha1>37053175b3b5e6666a27a0d7dfeead2bc33d491a</sha1>
  </revision>
</page>