<page>
  <title>To-Do list</title>
  <ns>0</ns>
  <id>802</id>
  <revision>
    <id>8954</id>
    <timestamp>2021-12-19T16:05:46Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="2470" space="preserve">Welcome to our To-Do list where we try and keep a track of everything which needs fixing/updating/adding/removing and anything else in any of the pages of the wiki. If you see something that needs to be done on any of the pages, feel free to edit this page and it in the below list or simply drop a message in our [https://discord.gg/a6DFe4p Discord] and someone else will do it.
&lt;br&gt;

We aim to one day have this page empty but it is not so easy unless everyone contributes a little.
&lt;br&gt;

Please do not delete the task if done, just write (DONE) before it so that one of the moderators can verify it.

== Uncategorized Tasks ==
# Update [[Shops]] and any other necessary pages to reflect new shops added as of V0.9.10
# Change all references of "Size is X by Y" in [[Dungeons]] and all Dungeon pages to read "Size is '''initially''' X by Y". Also consider how to detail chests, etc. as the number of chests/pokémon also decreases with size.
# Make a "Wiki Code Hunt" for the game codes. Trivia questions should be added in a way to encourage wiki engagement. Once the hunt is made an NPC can be added to the game referencing it.

== Categorized Tasks ==

These task are also put together with like tasks so multiple tasks on one page can be done by 1 person all at once rather than multiple people over a long period of time because of misplaced information.

''Page Creation'' is the creation of an entire page, and then adding all the information, adding lots of images to pages, or just large undertakings of fairly blank pages.
''Finishing Touches'' is for pages that are missing a small bit of info, or need to have a few images uploaded to them.
''Updating'' is for pages that were afflicted by the most recent update of the game, and thus have to be checked for informational inaccuracies.
''Formatting'' is for pages that would need to have their infoboxes changes, the way the information is display, or the general aesthetic changed.

=== Page Creation ===

== Dream tasks ==
These tasks are so long and such low priority that it is more of a dream to complete them.

# add battle item type template for other pages in these headings, "Key items", "shop of each region" and any more that can be put under same big heading.
# add Shiny Variants to the normal Pokémon and a way to swap between the images.  This is something that's up to debate, as there's little use for it other than being something for us to do.

== Completed tasks awaiting moderators ==</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>Jk13</username>
      <id>14</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>/* Uncategorized Tasks */</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>8953</parentid>
    <sha1>cc73eae9ca97039af23bdde24dfdfb098b64e14a</sha1>
  </revision>
</page>