<page>
  <title>Farm</title>
  <ns>0</ns>
  <id>191</id>
  <revision>
    <id>3210</id>
    <timestamp>2020-10-16T17:01:40Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="2517" space="preserve">[[File:Pokeclicker_Farm_Interface.png|400px|thumb|The Farm interface, with Cheri Berries selected. The "Buy new plot" button is absent as all plots have been unlocked.]]

The '''Farm''' is a location in Kanto where [[Berries]] can be planted. Harvesting them yields [[Pokemon Dollars|money]], [[Farming Points]], and more of the same type of Berry. The Farm is unlocked upon unlocking Route 14 of [[Kanto]] and obtaining the [[Wailmer pail]].

One of the quests that can appear involves harvesting a random amount of a certain type of Berry.

=Usage=

''For a breakdown of harvest yields for the various types of Berries, consult the [[Berries]] page.

Before completing Kanto, the Farm can be accessed by clicking on its location on the map between Routes 14 and 15, but upon reaching Johto, it becomes available in the Shortcuts dropdown list.

Berries are dropped by defeated Pokemon at random. They can be planted by selecting the desired type in the left-hand column and clicking on plots in the field on the right. Alternatively, the "Plant All" button can be clicked to plant the selected Berry in every empty plot.

Depending on the type of Berry planted, different lengths of time have to pass before they can be harvested. Individual plots can be clicked to be harvested, or the "Harvest All" button may be pressed to harvest every plot ready for harvesting.

=Upgrades=

Extra plots can be unlocked using Farming Points to allow more Berries to grow simultaneously, up to a maximum of 25.

{| class="wikitable"
|-
! Plots !! Cost in [[FP]] !! !! Plots !! Cost in [[FP]] !! !! Plots !! Cost in [[FP]] !! !! Plots !! Cost in [[FP]]
|-
| 1 to 2 || 10 {{Farmpoints}} || rowspan = 6 | || 7 to 8 || 490 {{Farmpoints}} || rowspan = 6 | || 13 to 14 || 1690 {{Farmpoints}} || rowspan = 6 | || 19 to 20 || 3610 {{Farmpoints}}
|-
| 2 to 3 || 40 {{Farmpoints}} || 8 to 9 || 640 {{Farmpoints}} || 14 to 15 || 1960 {{Farmpoints}} || 20 to 21 || 4000 {{Farmpoints}}
|-
| 3 to 4 || 90 {{Farmpoints}} || 9 to 10 || 810 {{Farmpoints}} || 15 to 16 || 2250 {{Farmpoints}} || 21 to 22 || 4410 {{Farmpoints}}
|-
| 4 to 5 || 160 {{Farmpoints}} || 10 to 11 || 1000 {{Farmpoints}} || 16 to 17 || 2560 {{Farmpoints}} || 22 to 23 || 4840 {{Farmpoints}}
|-
| 5 to 6 || 250 {{Farmpoints}} || 11 to 12 || 1210 {{Farmpoints}} || 17 to 18 || 2890 {{Farmpoints}} || 23 to 24 || 5290 {{Farmpoints}}
|-
| 6 to 7 || 360 {{Farmpoints}} || 12 to 13 || 1440 {{Farmpoints}} || 18 to 19 || 3240 {{Farmpoints}} || 24 to 25 || 5760 {{Farmpoints}}
|}</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>Adrian.Lew</username>
      <id>29</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>Added farm interface, expanded on info, tried to condense table</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>3209</parentid>
    <sha1>e82a9f41169b363d554637c47b8b5f0fe068557f</sha1>
  </revision>
</page>