<page>
  <title>Pokémon Day Care</title>
  <ns>0</ns>
  <id>1785</id>
  <revision>
    <id>10674</id>
    <timestamp>2021-01-02T04:42:13Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="3349" space="preserve">(Daycare interface image)

The '''Pokemon Day Care''' is a location in [[Kanto]] where [[Eggs]] and [[Fossils]] can be bred. Additionally, obtained [[List of Pokemons with attack|Pokémon]] that have reached level 100 can be bred to receive an Attack bonus equal to 25% of its Base Attack.  The Pokémon Day Care is unlocked upon clearing '''Route 5''' of [[Kanto]].

One quest that can appear involves hatching a random amount of Eggs. These can be either purchased from [[Shops]], or from breeding level 100 Pokémon.

=Usage=

As soon as [[Kanto#Routes|Route 5]] is cleared, the Pokemon Day Care can be accessed by clicking on its location on the map on Route 5. Additionally, the Hatchery tab (Which functions as a link to the Pokemon Day Care) becomes accessible on the main window.

There are three different types of hatch-able resources in Pokeclicker: obtained Pokémon Eggs, Fossils, and obtained level 100 Pokémon. Pokémon eggs are typically purchased in Shops, Fossils are typically mined from the [[Underground]], and obtained level 100 Pokémon are by definition already captured. The Egg/Fossil/Level 100 Pokémon that can be bred each have their own distinct window in the Pokemon Day Care. 

Clicking on the desired Egg/Fossil/Level 100 Pokémon will result in it being added to the Hatchery. The Hatchery only has 4 slots, but Breeding Queue slots can be unlocked in each new region (See Upgrades Below). The Breeding Queue automatically adds queued Pokémon to the Hatchery if there is space. If there is a Pokémon in the queue, Eggs/Fossils that are ready to hatch will do so and be replaced by the queued Pokémon.

Each Pokémon has a certain number of Egg Steps required before it can hatch from an Egg. Consult [[List of Pokemons with attack]] for egg steps for all Pokémon. Egg Steps are gained through defeating Pokémon. [[Regions|Route Statistics]], [[Gyms]], and [[Dungeons]] all yield different numbers of Egg Steps per Pokémon defeated, although the Egg Steps yielded generally scales with difficulty.

When an Egg/Fossil in the Hatchery has obtained the required number of Egg Steps, indicated by the green progress bar on each Egg/Fossil, it will be ready to hatch. Clicking on the image of the Egg/Fossil with hatch it, giving the player one of that Pokémon. 

[[Baby Pokémon]] are Pokémon obtained exclusively through Breeding the evolved stage of that Pokémon, the first time a Baby Pokémon is hatched the player will obtain both the original evolved stage, and the baby stage of that Pokémon.

The 25% increase to a Pokémon's Base Attack through breeding can be increased through the use of [[Protein]]. Proteins increase the Attack bonus from Breeding by 1 for each Protein used on an individual Pokémon. Consult [[Protein]] for further information on Breeding Efficiency using Proteins.

Breeding Pokémon offers much higher shiny odds than any other method of obtaining Pokémon in the game at 1/1024 using the Shiny Charm. Consult [[Shiny Chance]] for further information on Shiny Odds using the Hatchery.

=Upgrades=

Additional Breeding Queue slots can be obtained by progressing to the next region.

==Hatchery Queue Slots==
{| class="wikitable sortable" style
|-
! Region !! Number of Breeding Queue Slots
|-
| Kanto || 0
|-
| Johto || 4
|-
| Hoenn || 8
|-
| Sinnoh || 16
|-
| Unova || 32
|}</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>Jk13</username>
      <id>14</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>Initial Pokemon Day Care Page, Needs Image + lots of cleaning up</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>0</parentid>
    <sha1>49810cb06d21737676de8426b0e95d8c5262cfbd</sha1>
  </revision>
</page>