<page>
  <title>User:TailGlowVM</title>
  <ns>2</ns>
  <id>3450</id>
  <revision>
    <id>13208</id>
    <timestamp>2021-10-31T10:35:24Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="450" space="preserve">This is a test. I need to do 10 edits. I apologise for putting lots of unnecessary stuff in the changelog. I want to fix a few errors with the wiki. I might add a bit more strategy to some pages as well. I hope I can be helpful here. It would be good if you could be clear about this when talking about what to do if you want to edit. This is slow, useless and boring to do. Thank you for producing this great game. Right, that's it, off to edit now.</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>TailGlowVM</username>
      <id>38</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>13207</parentid>
    <sha1>81f02e00267932685898f8d5387218323376645b</sha1>
  </revision>
  <revision>
    <id>13207</id>
    <timestamp>2021-10-31T10:35:06Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="415" space="preserve">This is a test. I need to do 10 edits. I apologise for putting lots of unnecessary stuff in the changelog. I want to fix a few errors with the wiki. I might add a bit more strategy to some pages as well. I hope I can be helpful here. It would be good if you could be clear about this when talking about what to do if you want to edit. This is slow, useless and boring to do. Thank you for producing this great game.</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>TailGlowVM</username>
      <id>38</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>13206</parentid>
    <sha1>b807856c36a25a0958b6fcf1c454ae3d7c05097d</sha1>
  </revision>
  <revision>
    <id>13206</id>
    <timestamp>2021-10-31T10:34:42Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="374" space="preserve">This is a test. I need to do 10 edits. I apologise for putting lots of unnecessary stuff in the changelog. I want to fix a few errors with the wiki. I might add a bit more strategy to some pages as well. I hope I can be helpful here. It would be good if you could be clear about this when talking about what to do if you want to edit. This is slow, useless and boring to do.</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>TailGlowVM</username>
      <id>38</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>13205</parentid>
    <sha1>0ed0eac59f75137b389912c46e376d8a866e409a</sha1>
  </revision>
  <revision>
    <id>13205</id>
    <timestamp>2021-10-31T10:34:16Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="334" space="preserve">This is a test. I need to do 10 edits. I apologise for putting lots of unnecessary stuff in the changelog. I want to fix a few errors with the wiki. I might add a bit more strategy to some pages as well. I hope I can be helpful here. It would be good if you could be clear about this when talking about what to do if you want to edit.</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>TailGlowVM</username>
      <id>38</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>13204</parentid>
    <sha1>31fff660aae962a6716a3cbdf755aa740ee0f3df</sha1>
  </revision>
  <revision>
    <id>13204</id>
    <timestamp>2021-10-31T10:33:26Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="233" space="preserve">This is a test. I need to do 10 edits. I apologise for putting lots of unnecessary stuff in the changelog. I want to fix a few errors with the wiki. I might add a bit more strategy to some pages as well. I hope I can be helpful here.</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>TailGlowVM</username>
      <id>38</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>13203</parentid>
    <sha1>a9b1863f9a835fe1b6f7d9324d9c2dce83872a04</sha1>
  </revision>
  <revision>
    <id>13203</id>
    <timestamp>2021-10-31T10:33:07Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="203" space="preserve">This is a test. I need to do 10 edits. I apologise for putting lots of unnecessary stuff in the changelog. I want to fix a few errors with the wiki. I might add a bit more strategy to some pages as well.</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>TailGlowVM</username>
      <id>38</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>13202</parentid>
    <sha1>648b351ee0dad70007b416e156843a4f36189f23</sha1>
  </revision>
  <revision>
    <id>13202</id>
    <timestamp>2021-10-31T10:32:42Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="148" space="preserve">This is a test. I need to do 10 edits. I apologise for putting lots of unnecessary stuff in the changelog. I want to fix a few errors with the wiki.</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>TailGlowVM</username>
      <id>38</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>13201</parentid>
    <sha1>18d2e2612ba9080df1690201b483ee963be7366c</sha1>
  </revision>
  <revision>
    <id>13201</id>
    <timestamp>2021-10-31T10:32:24Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="106" space="preserve">This is a test. I need to do 10 edits. I apologise for putting lots of unnecessary stuff in the changelog.</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>TailGlowVM</username>
      <id>38</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>13200</parentid>
    <sha1>7af5d959008f474d1e71de4b2fa071e0e3a78904</sha1>
  </revision>
  <revision>
    <id>13200</id>
    <timestamp>2021-10-31T10:31:51Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="38" space="preserve">This is a test. I need to do 10 edits.</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>TailGlowVM</username>
      <id>38</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment></comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>13199</parentid>
    <sha1>9eca8d40e2321cab7e5fa243890201a2757f46dd</sha1>
  </revision>
  <revision>
    <id>13199</id>
    <timestamp>2021-10-31T10:16:21Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="14" space="preserve">This is a test</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>TailGlowVM</username>
      <id>38</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>Created page with "This is a test"</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>0</parentid>
    <sha1>a54d88e06612d820bc3be72877c74f257b561b19</sha1>
  </revision>
</page>