<page>
  <title>Code Contributors</title>
  <ns>0</ns>
  <id>304</id>
  <revision>
    <id>4357</id>
    <timestamp>2020-10-27T19:56:42Z</timestamp>
    <text bytes="2487" space="preserve">So, you want to contribute code yourself like the fine folks on the list on the Main Page?&lt;br&gt;
Please enjoy our unreasonably detailed and long guide on how to do exactly that!&lt;br&gt;
Brought to you courtesy of (the amazing, wonderful, talented) [[User:Liczale|Liczale]] who struggled to do this for almost 2 and a half hours!

# Install [https://nodejs.org/ NodeJS]
# Install [https://desktop.github.com/ Github for Desktop]
# Go to the [https://github.com/pokeclicker/pokeclicker/ PokeClicker GitHub Website]
# Click the Green button that says "Code"
# Copy the HTTPS brought up by the Code Button, by clicking the Clipboard Icon
# Open the GitHub for Desktop app
# Click "Clone a Repository from the Internet"
# Go to the "URL" tab and paste the HTTPS from the Code Button
# Add the Repository and wait for it to download
# Open the Repository Tab on the top of the screen in the Github for Desktop App
# Click "Open in Command Prompt"
# Click "Open Without Git"
# Click "Open in CMD"
# Go to the opened instance of CMD
# Type `npm clean-install` and press Enter
# Once the Install is done type `npm start` and press Enter
# After doing that your internet browser should launch a local instance of PokeClicker
# Open File Explorer and navigate to the newly cloned directory
#* Alternatively you can go to repository in the GitHub menu and click on "Show in Explorer"
# Find and open any *.ts file you wish to edit
# If prompted, open with Notepad
# Make any changes you wish
# Once you finish your changes hit Save
# Now go back to the CMD and type `npm run eslint-fix`
#* This should fix any issues with it, or it will point them out for you to fix.
# Go back to the GitHub Desktop app
# In the bottom left put a summary of the changes in the box and hit the bottom left blue button
#* Github will recognize files marked for change
# Now you should be on the Main page, if so click the blue button that says "Push Origin"
# Fork the Repository when it asks you to
# Click "Contribute to Parent Project"
# Lastly click the button that says "View on GitHub"
# In your internet browser click "Pull Requests"
# Click the green "New Pull Request" Button
# Click "compare changes" 
# Click "compare across forks"
# Press "Head Repository" select the option representing your fork
# Now hit the "Create Pull Request" button

Congratulations! You just finished your edits and published them for review! Please reach out to any of the authors found here https://github.com/orgs/pokeclicker/people</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>Jaahay</username>
      <id>82</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>Second draft</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>4356</parentid>
    <sha1>8fbc8674917aa647b61f12210e0bd908c4931db5</sha1>
  </revision>
</page>