<mediawiki xmlns="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/ http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11.xsd" version="0.11" xml:lang="en">
<page>
  <title>Discord Plays Pokéclicker</title>
  <ns>0</ns>
  <id>12183</id>
  <revision>
    <id>33912</id>
    <timestamp>2022-12-12T19:44:57Z</timestamp>
    <text space="preserve" bytes="1934">'''Discord Plays Pokéclicker''' is a community-driven version of Pokéclicker that can be played in the Pokéclicker Discord server.

{{Infobox battle item
|name       = Discord Plays Pokéclicker
|image      = [[File:Discord_Plays_Pokeclicker.png|thumb|300px]]
|caption    = Discord Plays Pokéclicker as viewed on the mobile version of Discord.
}}

It is a community-driven playing experience where everyone works together to advance in the game. The save used in this version of the game has the Regional Attack Debuff, Require Complete Pokédex, and No Click Attack challenges on.

==How to Play==
To play, you must first join the Discord Plays Pokéclicker voice channel.  Once you have joined the voice channel, you can click "Watch Stream" to watch the stream, and you can open the chat of the voice channel to view the game with the screen split into quadrants.  These quadrants are used to help locate the mouse in the game.  You can then use commands in the chat channel to help control and progress in the game.

===Commands===
The following table lists the commands on can use to control the game. The '''Help''' command can be used in the chat channel to list the commands available to use as well.

{| class="wikitable"
! Command !! Short form !! Use !! Needed input
|-
|Help/Play || N/A || Shows the available commands || N/A
|-
|Click || C || Makes the bot click on the coordinates provided || X and Y coordinates 
|-
|Scroll || S || Scroll the screen the indicated number of pixels || Number of pixels to move (positive numbers scrolls down and negative scrolls up) 
|-
|Key || K || Click the asked Keyboard key || A single letter of number
|-
|Route || N/A || Move the player to the selected route || A route number
|-
|Up/Down/Left/Right || U/D/L/R ||Press that direction key || N/A
|}

'''Note:''' Commands can be used with or without capital letters, but a space is needed between the command used and the input.</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>CooldudeOmega0</username>
      <id>25</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>play also displays comands</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>33422</parentid>
    <sha1>d2f2dad95000f23f7543a6cecb79d0aad3314825</sha1>
  </revision>
</page></mediawiki>