<mediawiki xmlns="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/ http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11.xsd" version="0.11" xml:lang="en">
<page>
  <title>Home Page</title>
  <ns>0</ns>
  <id>3</id>
  <revision>
    <id>5</id>
    <timestamp>2020-09-03T12:06:56Z</timestamp>
    <text space="preserve" bytes="1770">__NOTOC__
== Welcome to {{SITENAME}}! ==
This Main Page was automatically created by a wiki creator (a volunteer who created this wiki per a request), and it seems it hasn't been replaced yet.

=== For the bureaucrat(s) of this wiki ===
Hello, and welcome at your new wiki! Thank you for choosing Miraheze for the hosting of your wiki, and we hope you will enjoy our hosting.

You can immediately start working on your wiki, whenever you want.

Need help? No problem! We will help you with your wiki as needed. To make a start we have added a few links about working with MediaWiki:
* &lt;span class="plainlinks"&gt;[https://www.mediawiki.org/wiki/Special:MyLanguage/Help:Contents MediaWiki guide (e.g. navigation, editing, deleting pages, blocking users)]&lt;/span&gt;
* &lt;span class="plainlinks"&gt;[https://meta.miraheze.org/wiki/FAQ Miraheze FAQ]&lt;/span&gt;
*&lt;span class="plainlinks"&gt;[https://meta.miraheze.org/wiki/Request_features Request settings changes on your wiki. (Extensions and Logo/Favicon changes should be done through Special:ManageWiki on your wiki].&lt;/span&gt;

==== But Miraheze, I still don't understand X! ====
Well, that's no problem. Even if something isn't explained in the documentation/FAQ, we still are happy to help you. You can find us here:
* &lt;span class="plainlinks"&gt;[https://meta.miraheze.org/wiki/Help_center On our own Miraheze wiki]&lt;/span&gt;
* On IRC in #miraheze on irc.freenode.net ([irc://irc.freenode.net/#miraheze direct link]; [http://webchat.freenode.net?channels=%23miraheze webchat])

=== For a visitor of this wiki ===
Hello, the default Main Page of this wiki (this is the default Main Page) has not been replaced yet by the bureaucrat(s) of this wiki. The bureaucrat(s) might still be working on a Main Page, so please check this page again later!</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>MediaWiki default</username>
      <id>1</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>Create main page</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>0</parentid>
    <sha1>03568c50c66200a91cfa2ab7bcd1ff6d697d57cd</sha1>
  </revision>
</page></mediawiki>