<mediawiki xmlns="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/ http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11.xsd" version="0.11" xml:lang="en">
<page>
  <title>Pokérus</title>
  <ns>0</ns>
  <id>4271</id>
  <revision>
    <id>15212</id>
    <timestamp>2022-06-26T23:42:46Z</timestamp>
    <text space="preserve" bytes="2884">[[File:Charmander_infected.png|thumb|200px|A Shiny Charmander in the Hatchery, infected by Pokérus]]

==Description==
The Pokérus is a microscopic life-form that may attach to Pokémon, which your Kanto starting Pokémon will be infected with in Sinnoh. It is a beneficial mechanic that a Pokémon can obtain.  Your chosen Kanto starting Pokémon will be infected by the Pokérus after clearing Distortion World for the first time.  Once a Pokémon is infected by the Pokérus, it may gain Effort Values (EVs), which increase attack from that Pokémon.

==Spreading the Pokérus==
Spreading the Pokérus can only occur in the [[Pokémon Day Care]].  Currently, only the Pokémon chosen as your Kanto Starter is able to spread the Pokérus, and only manually breeding that starting Pokémon will allow the Pokérus to spread to other Pokémon being actively hatched at the same time.  Or in other words, put your infected starter Pokémon as well as another Pokémon or three you wish to infect in the day care, and so long as your starter Pokémon isn't ready to hatch yet, all other Pokémon currently being hatched will be infected by the Pokérus.

==Effort Values (EVs)==
EVs are a damage multiplying stat for each individual Pokémon that can currently only be seen in the Pokédex page for that Pokémon.  EVs for a Pokémon can currently only be increased by catching that Pokémon again after it has caught the Pokérus.  Gaining EVs can be done by catching a Pokémon on a [[Route Statistics|Route]], in a [[Dungeon]], or via [[Evolution Items]].  [[Breeding]] and [[Wandering Pokémon]] do not count for gaining EVs.


====EVs Gain====
Different methods of catching a Pokémon will give different amounts of EVs.  If the [[Challenge Mode|Slow EVs Challenge Mode]] is activated, you gain 10x less EVs.  &lt;br&gt;''Note: Shiny caught Pokémon gain 5x more EVs than listed below.''
{| class="wikitable"
! EVs gained || Slow EV Challenge || Catching Method
|-
| 0.1 || 0.01 || Route Pokémon
|-
| 0.2 || 0.02 || Dungeon Pokémon
|-
| 1 || 0.1 || Evolution Item
|}

====EV Damage Multipler====
EVs benefit the Player by increasing the amount of damage that a Pokémon does.  EVs multiply damage done by up to (but never quite reaching) 2x.  If your EV is below 50, you gain 1% extra damage per EV.  I.E. with 5 Effort Value, you have a 1.05x damage multiplier for that Pokémon.
{| class="wikitable"
! Effort Value || Pokémon Damage Multiplier
|-
| 50 || 1.5x
|-
| 85 || 1.6x
|-
| 172 || 1.7x
|-
| 375 || 1.8x
|-
| 824 || 1.9x
|-
| 1642 || 1.99x
|-
| ∞ || ~2x
|}

====EV Formulas====
'''When Effort Value below 50:''' &lt;br&gt;
&lt;math&gt;\colorbox{White}{$ \text{EV Damage Multiplier} = 1 + (\text{EV} / 100)$}&lt;/math&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
'''When Effort Value 50 or greater:''' &lt;br&gt;
&lt;math&gt;\colorbox{White}{$ \text{EV Damage Multiplier} = 1 + \text{Min}(1, ((\text{EV} - 30)^{0.075} - 0.75 ))$}&lt;/math&gt;</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>Dragonkin550</username>
      <id>27</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>/* EVs Gain */</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>15211</parentid>
    <sha1>ffa24d48b47c676024274511a4e2f0279a1493b8</sha1>
  </revision>
</page></mediawiki>