<mediawiki xmlns="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11/ http://www.mediawiki.org/xml/export-0.11.xsd" version="0.11" xml:lang="en">
<page>
  <title>Translations:Berries/20/en</title>
  <ns>1198</ns>
  <id>11038</id>
  <revision>
    <id>33175</id>
    <timestamp>2022-12-09T21:37:44Z</timestamp>
    <text space="preserve" bytes="3269">{| class="wikitable" | style="text-align: center;"
! Aura !! Effect !! Notes
|-
! Aura Boost
| Boosts aura effects of the 8 surrounding berries || &lt;center&gt; This aura can only be applied to a berry once and does not affect other berries with this effect.
|-
! Overgrow
| Plants a berry of the same type in one of the 8 surrounding empty plots || &lt;center&gt; Original berry needs to be ripe before this takes effect. &lt;br&gt; This counts as a mutation and is affected by the same mutation boosts.
|-
! Parasite
| Transforms a berry in one of the 8 surrounding berries into the same berry as the parasite || &lt;center&gt; Original berry needs to be ripe before this takes effect. &lt;br&gt; This counts as a mutation and is affected by the same mutation boosts. &lt;br&gt; Parasite only affects berries in the taller and later stages. Seed and sprout cannot be taken over. &lt;br&gt; The newly taken over berry will start its timer at the start of the same stage as it was taken over.
|-
! Death
| Causes the surrounding 8 berries to wither more quickly || &lt;center&gt; Only affects ripe berries. &lt;br&gt; Does not affect other berries with Death aura. &lt;br&gt; Effect does not stack.
|-
! Harvest Amount
| Changes the amount of berries obtained on harvest/wither for the 8 surrounding berries.|| &lt;center&gt; Effect is multiplicative and stacks with [[Rich Mulch]]
|-
! Growth Rate
| Changes growth/wither time of the 8 surrounding berries || &lt;center&gt; Effect is multiplicative and stacks with Death aura (once ripe), [[Sprayduck]], and [[Boost Mulch]] effects.
|-
! Replant Chance
| Changes the chance that any of the 8 surrounding berries will replant itself after withering || &lt;center&gt; Effect is multiplicative and stacks with [[Sprinklotad]]
|-
! Mutation Chance
| Changes the chance that any of the 8 surrounding plots will mutate a berry if possible || &lt;center&gt; Effect is multiplicative and stacks with [[Squirtbottle]] and [[Surprise Mulch]] effects. &lt;br&gt; Affects Overgrow and Parasite effects
|-
! Kasib Prevention
| Prevents berries from mutating into [[Kasib]] berries when they wither || &lt;center&gt; A single berry with this ability will affect the entire field
|-
! Wither Prevention
| Prevents other berries from withering while this is berry is ripe || &lt;center&gt; A single berry with this ability will affect the entire field. &lt;br&gt; Berries with this ability do not affect each other. &lt;br&gt; Once this berry withers or is harvested other berries will reset their timers from the beginning of the Ripe stage.
|-
! Egg Growth
| Increases the growth speed of eggs in the hatchery || &lt;center&gt; Effect is multiplicative over the whole field. &lt;br&gt; Effect stacks with [[Blaze Cassette]]
|-
! Shiny Chance
| Increases chance of finding [[Shiny Chance|Shiny Pokémon]]|| &lt;center&gt; Effect is multiplicative over the whole field. &lt;br&gt; Effect stacks with [[Shiny Charm]]
|-
! Attract Aura
| Increases chance of Pokémon [[Wandering Pokemon|wandering]] onto the farm || &lt;center&gt; Effect is multiplicative over the whole field
|-
! Roamer Chance
| Increases chance of finding [[Roaming Pokemon|Roaming Pokémon]] on routes || &lt;center&gt; Effect is multiplicative over the whole field
|-
! EV Gain
| Increases amount of [[Pokerus|EVs gained]] in all applicable situations. || &lt;center&gt; Effect is multiplicative over the whole field
|}</text>
    <contributor>
      <username>FuzzyBot</username>
      <id>133</id>
    </contributor>
    <comment>Importing a new version from external source</comment>
    <model>wikitext</model>
    <parentid>31159</parentid>
    <sha1>36bb1d2aa76ccce3104bd5389890242daf8e24e2</sha1>
  </revision>
</page></mediawiki>